<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="about_titles">
        <item>Prologue</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>Background</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>Purpose</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>Structure</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>The app</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>Operations</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
        <item>!skip</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="about_contents">
<!--Prologue-->
        <item>The Word Bank is owned by The Icelandic languages institute.</item>
        <item>It includes specialised software for registration and publication of glossaries.</item>
        <item>Authors get access to a registration system to work on their glossaries and add them to the group of other glossary public users of the word bank can search in.</item>
        <item>The Icelandic languages institute makes a contact with the authors of the glossaries for them to get free access to the registration system provided that the languages institute may publish the glossaries in the word bank on the internet.</item>
        <item>Authors retain the rights to their works and may publish them whenever and wherever they choose.</item>
<!--Background-->
        <item>On the meeting of the Icelandic languages institute with word committees 22. november 1979 the idea of an Icelandic wordbank, or a íðorðabanka, first emerged.</item>
        <item>The Icelandic language institute arranged the foundation of a preparation committee for such a word bank in the year 1980 and its creation has been intermittently worked on ever since.</item>
        <item>Early preparation of the wordbank involved defining the context of the íðorða glossary collection and computer entry with computer processing in mind. Every glossary, created by the languages institute or on behalf of it, has been computer registered according to a special system designed for this purpose.</item>
        <item>In the regulations of the Icelandic language institute and its operations, nr. 159/1987, according to 7. gr.: ,,The institute shall follow the development of íðorðabanks in other countries, prepare such a bank here and handle its operation.“</item>
        <item>Many causes delayed and made difficult the continuous development of the idea of a wordbank but with the emergence of the internet it became much simpler technically to start the project so that companies, institutions and individuals, anywhere in the world, could use such a wordbank on the internet.</item>
        <item>The matter gained momentum when the Icelandic language institute was given a three million krona grant from the Lýðveldissjóð in 1995 for the development of the word bank and a three million krona grant from the same fund for translators. The grants were to be payed over a period of three years.</item>
        <item>The institute hired a employee in october 1995 to work on these projects. The two projects are substantially intertwined as the institute takes the view that the wordbank on a computer network can be an invaluable tool for translators.</item>
        <item>In the year 1996 the institute got a grant of one million kronas from the Málræktar-fund to design a computer system for the wordbank and in the year 1997 the same fund gave a grant of 400 thousand krona to be used to transfer the glossaries between computer systems.</item>
        <item>The project also benefited from new computer equipment the institution acquired in 1994. It was a gift from the Mjólkursamsalan in Reykjavík which had decided to use a portion of its advertising funds to support the Icelandic Language Policy in this manner.</item>
        <item>According to contracts made to projects working on behalf of the ministry of education the Icelandic languages institute was given a grant in 2003–2004 to reprogram the word bank.</item>
        <item>The institutes wordbank was opened on the internet on 15. november 1997, a day before the Icelandic Language Day, almost exactly 18 years after the idea of íðorðabank first emerged at a meeting of the Institute with word committees.</item>
        <item>At that meeting people thought that the bank would be stored in a central computer with a network connection to other terminals. Since then much progress has happened in the world of computers. Despite that this idea regarding the structure of the bank is fundamentally the same.</item>
        <item>The difference is that the network is many times bigger and the outside terminals more numerous as the as the central computer is connected to the internet.</item>
<!--Purpose-->
        <item>One purpose of a word bank is to coordinate the terminological usage in both related and different fields; to collect terms, define and unify them to avoid the use of different names of the same concept.</item>
        <item>The Icelandic Word Bank does serve this purpose. It can give a general survey of Icelandic terminology and contemporary neologisms, thus adding to the coordination of both usage and definitions.</item>
<!--Structure-->
        <item>The Icelandic Word Bank is divided into two main sections, processing section and display section.Each section contains glossaries in different fields.</item>
        <item>The display section is publicly searchable/accessible on the World Wide Web and the processing section is the part where the owners and editors of different glossaries can update their work and create new glossaries.</item>
        <item>When the owner of a particular glossary is ready to publish his/her work the editor of the Word Bank can copy the glossary from the processing section to the display section and thus either add a new glossary or update an existing one.</item>
        <item>All glossaries contain terms in Icelandic. In the bilingual glossaries, apart from the Icelandic, the most common language is English, but many of the glossaries are multilingual and the most frequent additional languages are Danish, German, Norwegian, Swedish and French.</item>
        <item>Today there are 36 glossaries containing about 125.000 terms in the display section, all accessible to the user in a single search, and additional 13 glossaries at different stages in the processing section.</item>
        <item>The Icelandic Word Bank on the World Wide Web can be updated at all times wherever the editors of its data bases are located in the world, as long as they are connected to the Internet, and the editors and other users can use their favourite WWW browsers for editing and searching as they are not bound to one platform.</item>
<!--TheApp-->
        <item>In 2014 four students at the University of Iceland made an App for the Íðorðabanki.</item>
        <item>The App allows users access to the display section of the íðorðabanki on Android smart phones and tablets.</item>
<!--Operations-->
        <item>The Icelandic language institute handles the word bank and its operation falls under the scope of the  íðorða-department of the institute.</item>
        <item>Initially the wordbank was accessible for free, but fees where charged from 15. october 1998 onwards, almost a year after the wordbank opened</item>
        <item>Fees were dropped 3. janúar 2001 and now access is free to the public.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>