<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--Help string arrays-->
    <!--NOTE There are two string arrays for each section
    one including the titles and one including the contents.
    They will be displayed in order (first item in titles
    will be the title array for the first item in the content array.
    If you want to skip the title, put in an empty item in the title array-->
    <!--Titles for search fragment help -->
    <string-array name="help_search_fragment_titles">
        <item></item>
        <item>How to search</item>
        <item>Get more results</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Too many results?</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Contents for search fragments-->
    <string-array name="help_search_fragment">
        <item>The search is not case sensitive</item>
        <item>Type in a word in the search box and click search</item>
        <item>You can use the \'?\' character to substitute one character\n(m?nni would result in minni, mynni and munni)</item>
        <item>You can use the \'*\' character to substitute 0 or more characters\n(m*nni would result in minni, misminni,myndminni,…)</item>
        <item>When using the \'*\' character you have to specify at least two other characters in the search</item>
        <item>Go to the glossaries tab to restrict search to selected glossaries\n\n
        Go to the languages tab to restrict search to certain search- or target languages</item>

    </string-array>
    <!--Titles for search fragment help -->
    <string-array name="help_glossary_fragment_titles">
        <item></item>
        <item>Selecting a glossary</item>
        <item>Selecting all glossaries</item>
        <item>Glossary descriptions</item>
        <item>Restrictions</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Contents for search fragment help -->
    <string-array name="help_glossary_fragment">
        <item>By default all the glossaries are searched but the search can be restricted to one or more particular glossaries</item>
        <item>Just tap one or more glossary to select or deselect it, the glossaries with a check mark on the left are selected</item>
        <item>You can press the select all button to select all glossaries</item>
        <item>The button to the right of some glossaries is a link to a description of the glossary</item>
        <item>You have to select at least one glossary</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Titles for select language fragment-->
    <string-array name="help_language_fragment_titles">
        <item>Search language</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Target language</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Contents for select language fragment-->
    <string-array name="help_language_fragment">
        <item>By default the search searches in all languages</item>
        <item>You can restrict the search to a particular search language by pressing the drop down list for the search language and selecting a language</item>
        <item>You can only select one or all search languages</item>
        <item>By default the search displays results in all languages</item>
        <item>You can restrict the search to a particular target language by pressing the drop down list for the target language and selecting a language</item>
        <item>You can only select one or all target languages</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="help_result_screen">Implement Help here</string>

    <string name ="help_result_info_screen">1) Name of selected term\n
        2) The glossary this term belongs to \n
        3) Translations and all extra info contained in the glossary for this term is listed here.\n
            If extra information exists for a particular translation it is listed right below it inside a light green box. If similar terms exist they are listed below the light green box.
    </string>




</resources>